D2.
Read Vicky's article about her favourite season.
I love winter.
Winter is my favourite season.
It is very cold and everyone has to wear thick, warm clothes.
But I always enjoy winter here in Harbin.
During this season you cannot see colourful flowers.
The temperature is usually below zero and it is often snowy.
Everything is covered in deep white snow.
Even the lakes and rivers are frozen.
The land is quiet and beautiful.
My friends and I love to have big snowball fights.
We throw snowballs at each other, running and laughing.
We also make snowmen and use carrots for their noses.
They look funny.
Moreover, I enjoy the ice and snow festival each year.
There are beautiful ice sculptures everywhere.
Winter in Harbin is really great and there are many fun activities to do.
I love winter.